[{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980263150,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":12909,"timeElapsed":63971},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980274535,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":11382,"timeElapsed":75356},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980277840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3304,"timeElapsed":78661},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980285698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":7857,"timeElapsed":86519},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980290724,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5024,"timeElapsed":91545},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980297317,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":6592,"timeElapsed":98138},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980305540,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":8221,"timeElapsed":106361},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980323889,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":18349,"timeElapsed":124710},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980330204,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":6312,"timeElapsed":131025},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980338319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":7181,"timeElapsed":139140},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980347788,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":9468,"timeElapsed":148608},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980354178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":6388,"timeElapsed":154999},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980360637,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":6458,"timeElapsed":161458},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980363664,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3026,"timeElapsed":164485},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980432339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":68673,"timeElapsed":233160},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980435258,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2917,"timeElapsed":236079},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980440672,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5413,"timeElapsed":241493},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980444041,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3367,"timeElapsed":244862},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980449951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4978,"timeElapsed":250772},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980454465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4512,"timeElapsed":255286},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980460528,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":6063,"timeElapsed":261349},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980466561,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":6032,"timeElapsed":267382},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980469660,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3097,"timeElapsed":270481},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980478210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":8548,"timeElapsed":279031},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980483159,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4948,"timeElapsed":283980},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980557844,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":74684,"timeElapsed":358665},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980566922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":9076,"timeElapsed":367743},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980569071,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2148,"timeElapsed":369892},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980575492,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":5626,"timeElapsed":376313},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980578156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2663,"timeElapsed":378977},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980582741,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4583,"timeElapsed":383562},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980588799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":6057,"timeElapsed":389620},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980592575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3775,"timeElapsed":393396},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980597290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":4714,"timeElapsed":398111},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980599914,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2623,"timeElapsed":400735},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980609639,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":9723,"timeElapsed":410460},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980613624,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3984,"timeElapsed":414445},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980621761,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":7204,"timeElapsed":422582},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980624662,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2899,"timeElapsed":425483},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980628578,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3914,"timeElapsed":429399},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980645376,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":16797,"timeElapsed":446197},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980647298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":1921,"timeElapsed":448119},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980657162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":9862,"timeElapsed":457983},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980664779,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":7616,"timeElapsed":465600},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980721912,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":57131,"timeElapsed":522733},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980725481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3569,"timeElapsed":526302},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980731906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":5337,"timeElapsed":532727},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980734418,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2512,"timeElapsed":535239},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980736668,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2248,"timeElapsed":537489},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980741460,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":4792,"timeElapsed":542281},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980744262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2800,"timeElapsed":545083},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980749068,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":4805,"timeElapsed":549889},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980755157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":6088,"timeElapsed":555978},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980763389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":8231,"timeElapsed":564210},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980765052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1661,"timeElapsed":565873},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980776706,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":10965,"timeElapsed":577527},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980779217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2511,"timeElapsed":580038},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980785180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":5963,"timeElapsed":586001},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980789076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3894,"timeElapsed":589897},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980845508,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":56431,"timeElapsed":646329},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980848428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2919,"timeElapsed":649249},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980851477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3048,"timeElapsed":652298},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980855561,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":4083,"timeElapsed":656382},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980857655,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2093,"timeElapsed":658476},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980863571,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5065,"timeElapsed":664392},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980865758,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2186,"timeElapsed":666579},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980868995,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3236,"timeElapsed":669816},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980872664,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3668,"timeElapsed":673485},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980876267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3603,"timeElapsed":677088},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980879639,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3370,"timeElapsed":680460},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980901445,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":21804,"timeElapsed":702266},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980904263,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2816,"timeElapsed":705084},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980915058,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":10793,"timeElapsed":715879},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980918308,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3250,"timeElapsed":719129},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980931824,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":12470,"timeElapsed":732644},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980934733,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2907,"timeElapsed":735554},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980938441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3707,"timeElapsed":739262},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980946003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":7561,"timeElapsed":746824},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980951666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":5662,"timeElapsed":752487},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980959782,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":8115,"timeElapsed":760603},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980972950,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":13166,"timeElapsed":773771},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980985674,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":12722,"timeElapsed":786495},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980988751,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3075,"timeElapsed":789572},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980996551,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":6614,"timeElapsed":797371},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980999135,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2585,"timeElapsed":799956},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981005218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":6081,"timeElapsed":806039},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981008723,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3505,"timeElapsed":809544},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981014260,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5536,"timeElapsed":815081},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981018351,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4090,"timeElapsed":819172},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981025402,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":7051,"timeElapsed":826223},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981031935,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":6533,"timeElapsed":832756},{"subjectID":"0gpwxfjtpe","prolificID":"6021d9655d5b332710d8d984","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2605d628c0b7a282dfa","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981035033,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3096,"timeElapsed":835854}]